[

](https://ezcast-pro.com/ "EZCast Pro")

Toggle menu

Privacy Policy
==============

English

Chinese

English

Privacy Policy
==============

Effective date: April 11, 2018

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the https://www.ezcast.com/, related websites, EZCast, EZCast Pro and Quattro Meets applications (the “Service”).

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data. 

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

Definitions

* Personal Data

Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

* Usage Data

Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for  
example, the duration of a page visit).

* Cookies

Cookies are small pieces of data stored on a User’s device.

* Data Controller

Data Controller means a person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal data are, or are to be, processed.

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your data.

* Data Processor (or Service Providers)

Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any person (other than an employee of the Data Controller) who processes the data on behalf of  
the Data Controller. 

We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

* Data Subject

Data Subject is any living individual who is the subject of Personal Data.

* User

The User is the individual using our Service. The User corresponds to the Data Subject, who is the subject of Personal Data.

What Kind of Information Do We Collect?

We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

#### Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Email address
* First name and last name
* Phone number
* Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City
* Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send.

#### Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device (“Usage Data”).

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, bookmarks, videos watched, favorite videos, video playlists, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

#### Location Data

We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so (“Location Data”). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service.

You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.

#### Tracking Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* **Session Cookies.** We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
* **Preference Cookies.** We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
* **Security Cookies.** We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
* **Advertising Cookies.** Advertising Cookies are used to serve you with advertisements that may be relevant to you and your interests.

How Do We Use This Information?

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. uses the collected data for various purposes:

* To provide and maintain our Service
* To notify you about changes to our Service
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
* To provide customer support
* To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
* To monitor the usage of our Service
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues
* To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

How Long is This Information Retained?

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

How is This Information Shared?

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside China and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to China and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

How Do we Response to Legal Requests?

### Disclosure for Law Enforcement

Under certain circumstances, Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

### Legal Requirements

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
* To protect and defend the rights or property of Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
* To protect against legal liability

How Secure is Your Data?

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

How Can You Delete Or Mange Information About You?

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the right:

* To access and receive a copy of the Personal Data we hold about you
* To rectify any Personal Data held about you that is inaccurate
* To request the deletion of Personal Data held about you

You have the right to data portability for the information you provide to Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. You can request to obtain a copy of your Personal Data in a commonly used electronic format so that you can manage and move it.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

How Do We Share Information With Third-Party Partners?

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service (“Service Providers”), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

### Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service.

**Google Analytics**

Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on in general browser environment or changing settings in our apps. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**Flurry Analytics**

Flurry Analytics service is provided by Yahoo! Inc.

You can opt-out from Flurry Analytics service to prevent Flurry Analytics from using and sharing your information by changing settings in our apps.

For more information on the privacy practices and policies of Yahoo!, please visit their Privacy Policy page: [https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/policy/index.htm](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/policy/index.htm)

**Firebase**

Firebase is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports app usage. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by changing settings in our apps.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### Advertising

We may use third-party Service Providers to show advertisements to you to help support and maintain our Service.

**Google AdSense DoubleClick Cookie**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our Service. Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our Service or other websites on the Internet.

You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick Cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting the Google Ads Settings web page: [http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)

**AdMob by Google**

AdMob by Google is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out from AdMob by Google service by following the instructions described by Google: [https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)

For more information on how Google uses the collected information, please visit the “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or app” page: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) or visit the Privacy Policy of Google: [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

### Behavioral Remarketing

Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

**Google AdWords**

Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: [http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy Terms web page: [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**Facebook**

Facebook remarketing service is provided by Facebook Inc.

You can learn more about interest-based advertising from Facebook by visiting this page: [https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950)

To opt-out from Facebook’s interest-based ads follow these instructions from Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)

Facebook adheres to the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising established by the Digital Advertising Alliance. You can also opt-out from Facebook and other participating companies through the Digital Advertising Alliance in the USA [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), the Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada in Canada [http://youradchoices.ca/](http://youradchoices.ca/) or the European Interactive Digital Advertising Alliance in Europe [http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), or opt-out using your mobile device settings.

For more information on the privacy practices of Facebook, please visit Facebook’s Data Policy: [https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### Payments

We may provide paid products and/or services within the Service. In that case, we use third-party services for payment processing (e.g. payment processors).

We will not store or collect your payment card details. That information is provided directly to our third-party payment processors whose use of your personal information is governed by their Privacy Policy. These payment processors adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, Mastercard, American Express and Discover. PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of payment information.

The payment processors we work with are:

**PayPal**

Their Privacy Policy can be viewed at [https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

Links To Other Sites
--------------------

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children’s Privacy
------------------

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 (“Children”).

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

How Will We Notify You of Changes to This Policy?

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the “effective date” at the top of this Privacy Policy.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

How to Contact Us?

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

* By email: support@ezcast.com

Chinese

隐私政策
====

生效日期：2021年7月22日

炬力北方相关之所有子公司，包含深圳市炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）、北京炬力北方微电子股份有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）、广东省翼瞰集成电路设计有限公司（Guangdong EZMira Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）（“我们”）运营[https://www.ezcast.com/](https://www.ezcast.com/)、相关网站、EZCast、EZCast Pro和Quattro Meets移动应用程序（“服务”）。

当您使用我们的服务以及您与该数据相关的选择时，该页面会通知您有关收集、使用和披露个人数据的政策。

我们使用您的数据来提供和改进服务。通过使用该服务，您同意根据该政策收集和使用信息。除本隐私政策另有规定外，本隐私政策使用的术语与我们的条款和条件使用的同一术语具有相同的含义。

定义
--

### 个人数据

个人数据是指可以从这些数据（或者从我们拥有的或我们可能拥有的其他信息）中识别出某个人的此类数据。

### 使用数据

使用数据是通过使用服务或从服务基础设施本身生成的数据（例如，页面访问的持续时间）自动收集的数据。

### Cookies

Cookies是存储在用户设备上的一小段数据。

### 数据控制人

数据控制人是指（单独或联合或与他人共同）决定个人数据现在或将来的用途及处理方式的人。

数据控制人是指（单独或联合或与他人共同）决定个人数据现在或将来的用途及处理方式的人。

### 数据处理人（或服务提供商）

数据处理人（或服务提供商）是指代表数据控制人处理数据的任何人（数据控制人的雇员除外）。

为了更有效地处理您的数据，我们可以使用各种服务提供商的服务。

### 数据主体

数据主体是指作为个人数据主体的任何人。

### 用户

用户是使用我们服务的个人。用户对应于数据主体，即个人数据的主体。

我们收集哪类信息？

我们收集各类信息，用于给您提供并改进我们的服务。

#### 个人数据

在您使用我们的服务时，我们可能会要求您提供一些个人身份信息，这些信息可以用来联系您或识别您（“个人数据”）。个人身份信息可能包括但不限于：

* 电子邮件地址
* 姓和名
* 电话号码
* 地址，国家，省份，邮编，城市
* Cookies和使用数据

我们可以使用您的个人数据给您发送您可能感兴趣的时事通讯、营销或宣传材料和其他信息。您可以按照我们发送的任何电子邮件中提供的退订链接或说明，选择不接受来自我们的任何或所有这些通信。

#### 使用数据

当您访问我们的服务或当您通过移动设备访问我们的服务时，我们也可以收集您的浏览器发送的信息（“使用数据”）。

该使用数据包括您的计算机的互联网协议地址（例如IP地址）、浏览器类型、浏览器版本、您访问的服务页面、收藏夹、观看的视频、喜爱的视频、视频播放列表、您访问的时间和日期、花费在这些页面上的时间、唯一设备标识符和其他诊断数据等信息。

当您通过移动设备访问该服务时，在后台状态下，该使用数据包括您使用的移动设备的类型、您的移动设备的唯一ID、您的移动设备的MAC地址、您的移动设备的IP地址、您的移动操作系统、您使用的移动互联网浏览器的类型、唯一设备标识符和其他诊断数据等信息。

透过您的移动设备的唯一ID、您的移动设备的MAC地址、唯一设备标识符等资讯，製作临时的唯一ID来取得售后服务，包含客服服务、通知服务、书籤服务。

#### 位置数据

如果您允许，我们可以使用和存储您的位置信息(“位置数据”)。我们使用这些数据来为您提供我们的特色服务，并改进和为您定制我们的服务。

当您在任何时候使用我们的服务时，您可以通过您的设备设置启用或禁用位置服务。

#### 跟踪Cookies数据

我们使用Cookies和类似的跟踪技术来跟踪我们服务上的活动并保存某些信息。

Cookies是具有少量数据的文件，其中可能包括一个匿名的唯一标识符。Cookies从网站发送到您的浏览器并存储在您的设备上。跟踪技术还使用信标、标签和脚本来收集和跟踪信息，并改进和分析我们的服务。

您可以指示浏览器拒绝所有Cookies，或指示何时发送Cookies。但是，如果您不接受Cookies，您可能无法使用我们的某些服务。

我们使用的Cookies例子：

* **会话Cookies。** 我们使用会话Cookies来运作我们的服务。
* **偏好Cookies。** 我们使用偏好Cookies来记住您的偏好和各种设置。
* **安全Cookies。** 我们使用安全Cookies来保障安全。
* **广告Cookies。** 我们使用广告Cookies来为您提供可能与您和您的兴趣有关的广告。

我们如何使用这些信息？

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）将收集的数据用于：

* 提供和维护我们的服务
* 通知您我们服务的有关更改
* 允许您参与我们服务的互动功能，但前提是您选择这样做。
* 提供客户支持
* 收集分析数据或重要信息，以便改进我们的服务
* 监控我们服务的使用情况
* 检测、预防和解决技术问题
* 根据您已购买或查询的商品、服务和活动，向您提供我们提供的其他类似商品、服务和活动的新闻、特别优惠和一般信息，除非您已选择不接受此类信息。

这些信息可保留多长时间？

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）只会在本隐私政策规定用途所需的时间内保留您的个人数据。我们保留和使用您的个人数据只是为了履行我们的法律义务（例如，我们保留您的数据是为了遵守适用的法律）、解决纠纷并执行我们的法律协议和政策。

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）还将保留使用数据，用于进行内部分析。使用数据保留的时间通常较短，除非这些数据用于增强安全性或改善我们服务的功能，或者我们依据法律有义务将这些数据保留较长的时间。

这些信息如何共享？

您的信息，包括个人数据，可能会被传送到并保存在您所在州、省、国家或其他政府管辖区之外的计算机上，那里的数据保护法可能与您管辖区的数据保护法有所不同。

如果您在中国境外，并选择给我们提供信息，请注意，我们会把包括个人数据在内的数据传送到中国并在中国处理。

您同意本隐私政策后，提交这些信息即代表您同意该传送。

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）将采取一切必要的措施，确保根据本隐私政策安全处理您的数据，除有适当控制措施（包括保障您的数据和其他个人信息的安全性）外，您的个人数据不会被传送到任何组织或国家。

我们如何应对法律要求？

### 依法披露

在某些情况下，炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）可能需要依据法律或响应公共当局（如法院或政府机构）的有效要求披露您的个人数据。

### 法律要求

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）只要有合理理由认为以下情况所需，可能会披露您的个人数据：

* 遵守法律义务
* 保护并捍卫炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）的权利或财产。
* 防止或调查与服务有关的可能不当行为
* 保护服务用户和公众的人身安全
* 免于承担法律责任

您的数据有多安全？

您的数据的安全对我们来说至关重要，但请注意，经由互联网传输的任何方法或者任何电子存储方法均不是100%安全。虽然我们努力使用商业上可行的方法来保护您的个人数据，但我们不能保证其绝对安全。

您如何管理或删除有关您的信息？

炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）会采取一切合理的措施，以便让您更正、修改、删除您的个人数据或限制其使用。

只要可行，您可以在我们的网页或服务中，进入您的[帐户设置](https://auth.ezcast.com/)部分后直接更新您的个人数据，所有账号更正、修改或删除皆会在送出后马上生效。如帐号注销需联繫我司客服处理，联系方式为：support@ezcast.com ，帐号注销会于您申请后 5工作天处理完毕。

如果您无法更改您的个人数据，请与我们联系，以便作出所需的更改。

如果您想知道我们保留了您的哪些个人数据，而且您想让我们从我们的系统中删除这些数据，请联系我们。

在某些情况下，您有权：

* 在某些情况下，您有权：
* 纠正您的任何错误个人数据。
* 请求删除您的个人数据

您有权迁移您给炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）提供的信息。您可以请求获得一份常用电子格式的个人数据副本，以便于您管理和迁移这些数据。

请注意，我们可能会先让您证明您的身份，然后才会回应此类请求。

您如何管理摄像机权限？

### 目的

用户必须明确授予服务访问摄像头和麦克风的权限。首次使用该服务时，它会显示一条警报，要求授予您的应用访问相机的权限。

### iOS 相机权限控制

在设备的“设置”中找到“隐私”，然后轻点硬件功能，例如相机、蓝牙、本地网络或麦克风。  
该列表显示请求访问的应用程序。您可以打开或关闭列表中任何应用程序的访问权限。  
注意：每当应用程序使用麦克风（没有摄像头）时，屏幕顶部都会出现一个橙色指示器。每当应用程序使用相机时（包括相机和麦克风一起使用时），都会出现绿色指示器。此外，控制中心顶部会显示一条消息，通知您最近使用过应用程序。

### 安卓相机权限控制

在设置中找到应用管理，点击应用进行权限控制。选择您希望应用拥有的权限，例如相机或麦克风。您可以随时在设备上的主设置应用程序中更改应用程序可以访问的权限。请注意，关闭权限可能会导致您设备上的应用失去功能。

我们如何与第三方合作伙伴共享信息

我们可以雇用第三方公司和个人（“服务提供商”）来促进我们的服务，代表我们提供服务，执行与我们的服务相关的服务，或者协助我们分析我们的服务的使用情况。

这些第三方在代表我们执行这些任务时有权访问您的个人数据，并且有义务不披露这些数据或将其用于其他用途。

### 分析

我们可以使用第三方服务提供商来监控和分析我们的服务的使用情况。

**谷歌分析（Google Analytics）**

谷歌分析是由谷歌提供的Web分析服务，用于跟踪和报告网站流量。谷歌使用收集到的数据来跟踪和监视我们的服务的使用情况。此数据与其他谷歌服务共享。谷歌可以使用收集到的数据来让其自身广告网络上的广告呈现情境化和个性化。

您可以在常规浏览器环境中安装谷歌分析停用浏览器插件或在我们的应用程序中更改设置，从而选择停止将您在该服务上的活动提供给谷歌分析。该插件防止谷歌分析JavaScript(ga.js, analytics.js, 和 dc.js)与谷歌分析共享访问活动的信息。

有关谷歌隐私实践的更多信息，请访问谷歌隐私条款网页： [http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**Flurry分析**

Flurry分析服务由雅虎公司提供。

您可以在我们的应用程序中更改设置，退出Flurry分析服务，以防Flurry分析使用和共享您的信息。

有关雅虎隐私实践和政策的更多信息，请访问雅虎隐私政策页面：[https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/policy/index.htm](https://policies.yahoo.com/us/en/yahoo/privacy/policy/index.htm)

**Firebase**

Firebase是由谷歌提供的Web分析服务，用于跟踪和报告应用程序使用情况。谷歌使用收集到的数据来跟踪和监视我们的服务的使用情况。此数据与其他谷歌服务共享。谷歌可以使用收集到的数据来让其自身广告网络上的广告呈现情境化和个性化。

您可以在我们的应用程序中更改设置，从而选择停止将您在该服务上的活动提供给谷歌分析。

有关谷歌隐私实践的更多信息，请访问谷歌隐私条款网页：[http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

### 广告

我们可以使用第三方服务提供商向您发布广告，以帮助支持和维护我们的服务。

**谷歌AdSense DoubleClick Cookie**

谷歌作为第三方供应商，使用Cookie推送我们服务的广告。谷歌使用DoubleClick cookie使其及其合作伙伴能够根据我们的用户访问我们的服务或互联网上其他网站的情况向我们的用户推送广告。

您可以访问谷歌广告设置网页：[http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/)，选择退出使用基于兴趣的广告的DoubleClick Cookie

**谷歌AdMob**

谷歌AdMob 由谷歌公司提供。

您可以选择退出谷歌AdMob服务，具体操作见谷歌说明：[https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en)

有关谷歌如何使用所收集信息的更多信息，请访问“谷歌在您使用我们的合作伙伴的站点或应用程序时如何使用数据”页面：[http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)或访问谷歌的隐私政策：[http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

### 行为再营销

在您访问我们的服务后，炬力北方微电子有限公司（Actions Microelectronics Co., Ltd.）使用再营销服务在第三方网站上向您推送广告。我们和我们的第三方供应商根据您过去访问我们的服务的数据，使用Cookies来通知、优化和推送广告。

**Google AdWords**

谷歌AdWords再营销服务由谷歌公司提供。

您可以退出谷歌分析显示广告，并通过访问谷歌广告设置页面：[http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads)来定制谷歌显示网络广告

谷歌还建议为您的Web浏览器安装谷歌分析选择退出浏览器插件（Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on）- [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)。谷歌分析选择退出浏览器插件可让访问者防止谷歌分析收集和使用其数据。

有关谷歌隐私实践的更多信息，请访问谷歌隐私条款网页：[http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

**脸书（Facebook）**

脸书再营销服务由脸书公司提供。

您可以访问本页面：[https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950](https://www.facebook.com/help/164968693837950)了解脸书发布的更多基于兴趣的广告

按照脸书说明： [https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217)，选择退出脸书的基于兴趣的广告

脸书遵循由数字广告联盟建立的在线行为广告自律原则。您可以通过美国的数字广告联盟[http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/)、加拿大的加拿大数字广告联盟[http://youradchoices.ca/](http://youradchoices.ca/)、欧洲的欧洲互动数字广告联盟[http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)或使用您的移动设备设置选择退出脸书和其他参与公司。

有关脸书隐私实践的更多信息，请访问脸书数据政策：[https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

### 付款

我们可以在服务范围内提供有偿产品和/或服务。对于这种情况，我们使用第三方付款处理服务（如付款处理方）。

我们不会存储或收集您的支付卡的信息。这些信息直接提供给我们的第三方付款处理方，他们会根据他们的隐私政策使用您的个人信息。这些支付处理方遵循PCI DSS在PCI安全标准理事会（由Visa、万事达、美国运通和Discover等品牌共同成立的一个理事会）管理下设定的标准。PCI DSS要求有助于确保安全处理支付信息。

与我们合作的付款处理方是：

**PayPal**

有关他们的隐私政策，可访问[https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full)

链接到其他网站
-------

我们的服务可能包含并非由我们运作的其他网站链接。如果您点击了第三方链接，您会进入第三方网站。我们强烈建议您查阅您访问的每个网站的隐私政策。

我们无法控制任何第三方网站或服务的内容、隐私政策或实践，也不承担任何相关责任。

儿童隐私
----

我们不向13岁以下儿童（“儿童”）提供服务。

我们不会有意收集13岁以下儿童的个人身份信息。如果您是家长或监护人，并且您知道您的孩子向我们提供了个人数据，请与我们联系。如果我们发现我们未经家长同意收集了儿童的个人数据，我们会采取措施从我们的服务器中删除这些信息。

我们如何告知您本政策的变更？

我们可能会不时地更新我们的隐私政策。我们会在本页面发布新的隐私政策，以将隐私政策的任何变更告知您。

在变更生效之前，我们将通过电子邮件和/或在我们服务的显眼地方发布通知，以告知您此类变更，并在隐私政策的顶部更新“生效日期”。

建议您定期查看本隐私政策，以了解是否有任何变更。本隐私政策的任何变更在本页面公布时开始生效。

如何联系我们？

如果您对本隐私政策有任何疑问，请联系我们：

* 电子邮件： support@ezcast.com
* 访问我们网站的此页面： https://auth.ezcast.com/privacy

### Products

### Support

### Resources

### About

© 2024 EZCast Pro. Proudly powered by [Sydney](https://athemes.com/theme/sydney/)

We use cookies to offer an improved online experience and offer you content and services adopted to your interests. By using EZCast Pro you are giving your consent to our [Privacy Policy](https://ezcast-pro.com/privacy-policy/). Cookie settingsACCEPT

Privacy & Cookies Policy

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are as essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.

SAVE & ACCEPT

Our Spring Sale Has Started

You can see how this popup was set up in our step-by-step guide: https://wppopupmaker.com/guides/auto-opening-announcement-popups/

×

[

](https://ezcast-pro.com/contact-us/)

Interested in wireless conferencing system and would like to talk to our experts?
